linkatopia.com 2014-05-21

# Linkatopia - Privacy Policy, Sep 1, 2012

This document sets forth the Design215 Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this Web site, www.Linkatopia.com (the "Site"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or other Design215 web sites.

**Collection of personal information**  
Personal information on this Site is collected by Design215 Incorporated. Design215's address is 3015 North Ocean Boulevard, Suite C-115A, Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308 and its telephone number is +1 954 630.3695.

**Design215 will not send you any email regarding other products, services, or special offers, although we may communicate with you regarding your use of the services on this Site. Design215 will not provide your personal information to other companies or organizations without your consent.**

**How personal information is used**  
Design215 collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users.

Design215 may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected without identifying any user individually. Design215 may use this non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

**Service announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send all registered users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, but they are not promotional in nature.

**Legal Responsibility**  
Design215 may provide your personal information if necessary, in Design215's good faith judgement, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of Design215 or others.

**Protection of your personal information**  
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of Design215 products or services is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, for example in a chat room, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**Links to other sites**  
This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Design215 is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Use of cookies**  
When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we may use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, and enables Design215 to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)

**Log files**  
In addition to standard server log files, this site generates its own log files. These log files provide usernames, date/time stamp, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, platform type, and other statistical information. None of the information in Linkatopia log files is linked to personally identifiable information.

**Changes in privacy policy**  
All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Design215 reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the homepage of the Site for thirty (30) days.

**Business transitions**  
In the event Design215 is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, Design215 may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of the business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.

**Inquiries and complaints**  
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Design215 Inc. at:

Design215 Inc.  
3015 North Ocean Blvd.  
Suite C-115A  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33308

tel +1 954 630.3695  
fax +1 954 566.6155
